Guide to the Fales Manuscript Collection circa 1700-2000 MSS.001
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Letter sized boxes, 47643
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. A - P: Fools Paradise [English, 2 TS.], undated; 48436 (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. A - P: Das Gehintechts [MS. Yiddish] (The Scum - those living in the lowest depth), undated; 48435 (Box 160, Folder 9)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. A - P: Getzel the Monkey [English, TS. with corrections], undated; 48434 (Box 160, Folder 10)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. A - P: Grandmother's Tale [English, 2 TSS. and MS. additions], undated; 48433 (Box 160, Folder 11)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. A - P: Henne Fire [English, TS. with corrections], undated; 48432 (Box 160, Folder 12)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. A - P: I Place my Reliance in Man [English tr. by Ruth Whitman with Singer's MS. corrections], undated; 48431 (Box 160, Folder 13)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. A - P: Jachid and Jedidah [MS. Yiddish and English TS. with corrections; 3 versions], undated; 48430 (Box 160, Folder 14)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. A - P: Joseph and Koza [English tr.], undated; 48429 (Box 160, Folder 15)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. A - P: The Magic Circle [English], undated; 48428 (Box 160, Folder 16)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. A - P: Der Kuntzmacher tun Lublin (The Magician of Lublin)[Yiddish], undated; 48427 (Box 160, Folder 17)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. A - P: Mazel and Shlimazel [English, 2 TSS. with corrections; see also Galleys in File C, 2], undated; 48426 (Box 160, Folder 18)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. A - P: The Mixed-Up Feet and the Silly Bridegroom [English; 2 TSS.], undated; 48425 (Box 160, Folder 19)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. A - P: A Murder [MS. Yiddish], undated; 48424 (Box 160, Folder 20)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. A - P: Myses fun Hintern Oyven (Stories from Behind the Stove)[MS. Yiddish], undated; 48423 (Box 160, Folder 21)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. A - P: The Needle [English TS. with corrections], undated; 48422 (Box 160, Folder 22)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. A - P: One Day of Pleasure [Yiddish], undated; 48421 (Box 160, Folder 23)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. A - P: The Parrot [English TS. with corrections], undated; 48420 (Box 160, Folder 24)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. A - P: Pigeons [English], undated; 48419 (Box 160, Folder 25)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. A - P: Power [English] [see V.F. c/2], undated; 48418 (Box 160, Folder 26)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. S - Z: The Seance [English TS. and 2 drafts], undated; 48417 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. S - Z: The Snow in Chelm [English, 2 TSS.], undated; 48416 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. S - Z: The Son [English, 2 TSS.], undated; 48415 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. S - Z: A Tale of Two Sisters, undated; 48414 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. S - Z: Three Tales [English], undated; 48413 (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. S - Z: Under the Knife [English], undated; 48412 (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. S - Z: The Wardrobe [Yiddish], undated; 48411 (Box 161, Folder 7)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. S - Z: Yanda [English], undated; 48410 (Box 161, Folder 8)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. S - Z: Yentl [MS. Yiddish], undated; 48409 (Box 161, Folder 9)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. S - Z: Yentle the Yeshiva Boy [Yiddish MS.; Yiddish TS.; 2 English TSS.], undated; 48408 (Box 161, Folder 10)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. S - Z: Zeitel and Rickel [English], undated; 48407 (Box 161, Folder 11)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): MSS. S - Z: Zlateh the Goat [English], undated; 48406 (Box 161, Folder 12)
  - Singer, Isaac Bashevis (1904-1991): Correspondence to NYU, undated; 48405 (Box 161, Folder 13)
  - Sitwell, Edith, Dame, undated; 48404 (Box 162, Folder 1a)
  - Sitwell, Osbert, Sir, undated; 48403 (Box 162, Folder 1b)
  - Skariatuia, Irina (Blakeslee), undated; 48402 (Box 162, Folder 1c)
  - Skeat, Walter William, undated; 48401 (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Sladen, Douglas Brooke Wheelton, undated; 48400 (Box 162, Folder 3a)
  - Slim, William, undated; 48399 (Box 162, Folder 3b)
  - Sloan, William Milligan, undated; 48398 (Box 162, Folder 3c)
  - Smaley, J. M., undated; 48397 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Smedley, Francis Edward, undated; 48396 (Box 162, Folder 3e)
  - Smellie, William, undated; 48395 (Box 162, Folder 4a)
  - Smirke, Robert, Sir, undated; 48394 (Box 162, Folder 4b)
  - Smith, Albert Richard, undated; 48393 (Box 162, Folder 4c)
  - Smith, Anker, undated; 48392 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - [Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: see Boxes 163-167.5.A and Legal & Oversize], 1690-2000; 48391 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_24bd8acc952f1af88309e3d29a1fc568)
  - Smith, C. Roche, undated; 48390 (Box 162, Folder 4e)
  - Smith, Charles Roach, undated; 48389 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Smith, Charlotte, undated; 48388 (Box 162, Folder 5a)
  - Smith, Clark Ashton, undated; 48387 (Box 162, Folder 5b)
  - Smith, Frances Hopkinson, undated; 48386 (Box 162, Folder 6a)
  - Smith, Goldwin, undated; 48385 (Box 162, Folder 6b)
  - Smith, John, undated; 48384 (Box 162, Folder 6c)
  - Smith, Joseph P. of Urbana (Ohio) Daily Citizen, undated; 48383 (Box 162, Folder 7a)
  - Smith, Logan Pearsall, undated; 48382 (Box 162, Folder 7b)
  - Smith, Margaret Chase, undated; 48381 (Box 162, Folder 7c)
  - Smith, Samuel Francis [see also Legal Size], undated; 48380 (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - Smith, Sydney Goodsir: MS. Robert Burns and the Merry Muses of Caledonia, undated; 48379 (Box 162, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Sydney Goodsir: MS. Is there a Scottish Renaissance?, undated; 48378 (Box 162, Folder 10)
  - Smith, Sydney Goodsir: MS. King Stobo, undated; 48377 (Box 162, Folder 11)
  - Smith, Sydney Goodsir: MS. Kirkcaldy Lectures [1-3], undated; 48376 (Box 162, Folder 12)
  - Smith, Sydney Goodsir: MS. Kirkcaldy Lectures [4 & 8], undated; 48375 (Box 162, Folder 13)
  - Smith, Sydney Goodsir: Poems (MSS.): Omens; Celebrate the Seasons, undated; 48374 (Box 162.5, Folder 1)
  - Smith, Sydney Goodsir: MS. The Wallace [Act I - II], undated; 48373 (Box 162.5, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Sydney Goodsir: MS. The Wallace [Act III - V], undated; 48372 (Box 162.5, Folder 3)
  - Smith, William Sidney, Sir: 1 A.L.s., undated; 48371 (Box 162.5, Folder 4)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Argles - Balston [see also Legal & Oversize], undated; 48370 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Beadon - Bryce, undated; 48369 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Carr - Colebrook, undated; 48368 (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Colebrooke - Creagh, undated; 48367 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Creighton - Deane, undated; 48366 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Dedel - Fearn, undated; 48365 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Field - Gosling, undated; 48364 (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Gosling - Gunning, undated; 48363 (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Hadler - Ilbert, undated; 48362 (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Jackson - Jowett, undated; 48361 (Box 163, Folder 10)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Kennicott - Leigh, Cholmeley, undated; 48360 (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Leigh, Edward - Leigh, Emma Smith-Austen, undated; 48359 (Box 163, Folder 12)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Leigh, James Edward Austen - LeMarchant, Helen A., undated; 48358 (Box 163, Folder 13)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from LeMarchant, Sarah Eliza [Smith], undated; 48357 (Box 163, Folder 14)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Leyland - Northbrook, undated; 48356 (Box 163.5, Folder 1)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Paget - Scott, undated; 48355 (Box 163.5, Folder 2)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Selwyn - Seymour, Elizabeth, undated; 48354 (Box 163.5, Folder 3)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Seymour, Frances (Smith), 1805-1837; 48353 (Box 163.5, Folder 4)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Seymour, Frances (Smith), 1838-1871; 48352 (Box 163.5, Folder 5)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Seymour, Frances (Smith), undated; 48351 (Box 163.5, Folder 6)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Seymour, F. M. - Seymour, Laura M. Culme, undated; 48350 (Box 163.5, Folder 7)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Seymour, Maria Louisa Smith Culme, 1834-1850; 48349 (Box 163.5, Folder 8)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Seymour, Maria Louisa Smith Culme, 1852-1867; 48348 (Box 163.5, Folder 9)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Seymour, Michael - Seymour, Sissy Culme, undated; 48347 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Smith, Augusta Spencer, 1809-1831; 48346 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Smith, Augusta Spencer, 1832-1844; 48345 (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Smith, C. - Smith, L. M., undated; 48344 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Smith, Mary, 1826-1839; 48343 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Smith, Orlando Spencer - Smith, Spencer, 1814-1830; 48342 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Smith, Spencer, 1831-1839; 48341 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Smith, Spencer - Smith, W. H., 1839-1870; 48340 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Spooner-Thring, Henry, undated; 48339 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Walgrave - Webster [see also Oversize], undated; 48338 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Wilder, Augusta Smith [see also Smith, Augusta Spencer], undated; 48337 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Wilder, Charles - Yonge, Charlotte, undated; 48336 (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Unidentified, undated; 48335 (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence to Hodgson, Emily (Mrs. W. B. Hodgson), undated; 48334 (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Diaries [1802, 1803]: Smith, Augusta, 48333 (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Diaries [1805, 1824]: Smith, Augusta, 48332 (Box 166, Folder 7)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: MS. Jamaica, 1865; 48331 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: MS. Description of South Wales, undated; 48330 (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: MS. Poems, undated; 48329 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Genealogies: Smith Family, undated; 48328 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Printed Materials, undated; 48327 (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Christmas Cards, undated; 48326 (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Miscellaneous Greeting Cards, undated; 48325 (Box 167, Folder 7)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Miniature Newspapers, undated; 48324 (Box 167, Folder 8)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Newspaper Clipping, undated; 48323 (Box 167, Folder 9)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Silouettes [sic], undated; 48322 (Box 167, Folder 10)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Water Colors and Drawings, undated; 48321 (Box 167, Folder 11)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographs: Artifacts, Bookplates, miscellaneous, undated; 48320 (Box 167, Folder 12)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographs: Churches, undated; 48319 (Box 167, Folder 13)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographs: Houses and People in group shots, undated; 48318 (Box 167, Folder 14)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographs: Jamaica, undated; 48317 (Box 167, Folder 15)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographs: Towns and Cities, undated; 48316 (Box 167, Folder 16)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographic: Children and Pets, undated; 48315 (Box 167, Folder 17)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographic: Men and Groups, undated; 48314 (Box 167.5, Folder 1)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographic: Women, undated; 48313 (Box 167.5, Folder 2)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Correspondence from Smith, Spencer [8(a)], undated; 48312 (Box 167.5, Folder 3)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Legal Documents [8(b)], undated; 48311 (Box 167.5, Folder 4)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: MS. Funeral Procession of Seymour, Sir Michael, Rear Admiral [8(c)], undated; 48310 (Box 167.5, Folder 5)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Song The King of Merry England [Gilfillan, Robert (1798-1850)], undated; 48309 (Box 167.5, Folder 6)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographic Album [1], undated; 48308 (Box 167.5.A, Folder 1)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographic Album [2], undated; 48307 (Box 167.5.A, Folder 2)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographic Album [3], undated; 48306 (Box 167.5.A, Folder 3)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographic Album [4], undated; 48305 (Box 167.5.B, Folder 1)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: Photographic Album [5], undated; 48304 (Box 167.5.B, Folder 2)
  - Smith and Austen-Leigh Papers: handwritten Italian book, undated; 48303 (Box 167.5.B, Folder 3)
  - Snaith, John Collis, undated; 48302 (Box 168, Folder 1a)
  - Snow, C. P., undated; 48301 (Box 168, Folder 1b)
  - Soder, J. H., undated; 48300 (Box 168, Folder 1c)
  - Somerville, Edith Anne O'Enone, undated; 48299 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Somerville, Mary Fairfax, undated; 48298 (Box 168, Folder 1e)
  - Sonon, ______?, undated; 48297 (Box 168, Folder 2a)
  - Sotheby, William, undated; 48296 (Box 168, Folder 2b)
  - Sothern, Edward Askew (1826-1881), undated; 48295 (Box 168, Folder 2c)
  - Soutar, William: MS. Lyrics in English [1926-1933], 48294 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Southey, Robert, undated; 48293 (Box 168, Folder 4a)
  - Southworth, Emma Dorothy Eliza, undated; 48292 (Box 168, Folder 4b)
  - Sparks, Jared, undated; 48291 (Box 168, Folder 5a)
  - Spence, W., undated; 48290 (Box 168, Folder 5b)
  - Spender, John, undated; 48289 (Box 168, Folder 5c)
  - Spender, Stephen, undated; 48288 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - Spielmann, Marion Harry, undated; 48287 (Box 168, Folder 5e)
  - Spingarn, Joel Elias (1875-1939), undated; 48286 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - Spofford, A. R., undated; 48285 (Box 168, Folder 6a)
  - Spofford, Harriet P., undated; 48284 (Box 168, Folder 6b)
  - Spooner, John, undated; 48283 (Box 168, Folder 6c)
  - Sprague, Charles, undated; 48282 (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - Sprague, William Buell, undated; 48281 (Box 168, Folder 6e)
  - Sprigge, Elizabeth, undated; 48280 (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - Spurgeon, Charles Haddon, undated; 48279 (Box 168, Folder 7a)
  - Squire, John Collings, Sir, undated; 48278 (Box 168, Folder 7b)
  - Stacpoole, Henry de Vere, undated; 48277 (Box 168, Folder 7c)
  - Stae¨l-Holstein, Anne Louise Germaine (Necker), undated; 48276 (Box 168, Folder 7)
  - Stainer, John, Sir, undated; 48275 (Box 168, Folder 8a)
  - Stanfield, Clarkson, undated; 48274 (Box 168, Folder 8b)
  - Stanton, Elizabeth Cady, undated; 48273 (Box 168, Folder 8c)
  - Starrett, Vincent, undated; 48272 (Box 168, Folder 8)
  - Stedman, Edmund Clarence, undated; 48271 (Box 168, Folder 9a)
  - Steel, Flora Anne (Webster), undated; 48270 (Box 168, Folder 9b)
  - Stein, Gertrude, undated; 48269 (Box 168, Folder 10)
  - Steinbeck, John, undated; 48268 (Box 168, Folder 11a)
  - Stephen, Leslie, Sir, undated; 48267 (Box 168, Folder 11b)
  - Stephens, Frederic George, undated; 48266 (Box 168, Folder 11c)
  - Stephens, James, undated; 48265 (Box 168, Folder 11)
  - Stephens, Kate, undated; 48264 (Box 168, Folder 12a)
  - Stephens, Kate: Notes and Commentary to The Professor's Love-Life, undated; 48263 (Box 168, Folder 12b)
  - Stepney, C. S., undated; 48262 (Box 168.5, Folder 1a)
  - Stepney, Catherine, Lady, undated; 48261 (Box 168.5, Folder 1b)
  - Sterling, George, undated; 48260 (Box 168.5, Folder 1c)
  - Sterne, Lawrence, undated; 48259 (Box 168.5, Folder 1)
  - Stevenson, Burton Egbert, undated; 48258 (Box 168.5, Folder 1e)
  - Stevenson, Fanny (Van de Grift), undated; 48257 (Box 168.5, Folder 1)
  - Stevenson, J. H., undated; 48256 (Box 168.5, Folder 1g)
  - Stevenson, Robert Louis, undated; 48255 (Box 168.5, Folder 2a)
  - Stevenson, Robert Louis: Pictorial Treasure Island, undated; 48254 (Box 168.5, Folder 2b)
  - Stevenson, Robert Louis: Woodcuts/Proofs, undated; 48253 (Box 168.5, Folder 3)
  - Stevenson, Robert Louis: MSS. Music [transcript of Schubert], undated; 48252 (Box 168.5, Folder 4)
  - Stewart, C. D., undated; 48251 (Box 168.5, Folder 5a)
  - Stewart, D. J., undated; 48250 (Box 168.5, Folder 5b)
  - Stirling-Maxwel, William, Sir, undated; 48249 (Box 168.5, Folder 5c)
  - Stockley, Cynthia, undated; 48248 (Box 168.5, Folder 5)
  - Stockton, Frank Richard, undated; 48247 (Box 168.5, Folder 5e)
  - Stoddard, Charles Warden, undated; 48246 (Box 168.5, Folder 5)
  - Stoddard, Henry, undated; 48245 (Box 168.5, Folder 5g)
  - [Stoker, Bram: see Box 169], 1690-2000; 48244 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_b52ce0f1320a029a334af690cf7e92d0)
  - Stoppard, John L., undated; 48243 (Box 168.5, Folder 6a)
  - Stoppard, Richard Henry, undated; 48242 (Box 168.5, Folder 6b)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): Correspondence: 2 A.L.s.; 3 Telegrams, undated; 48241 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): Correspondence to E. Robins, undated; 48240 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): MS. The Lair of the White Worm [Chapters 1-15], undated; 48239 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): MS. The Lair of the White Worm [Chapters 16-30], undated; 48238 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): MS. The Lair of the White Worm [Chapters 31-41], undated; 48237 (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): MS. Under the Sunset, undated; 48236 (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): Pamphlet Under the Sunset, undated; 48235 (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): MS. "Invisible Giant" in Under the Sunset, undated; 48234 (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): MS. "The Rose Prince" in Under the Sunset, undated; 48233 (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): MS. "The Shadow Builder" in Under the Sunset, undated; 48232 (Box 169, Folder 10)
  - Stoker, Bram (1847-1912): MS. "The Wondrous Child" in Under the Sunset, undated; 48231 (Box 169, Folder 11)
  - Stokes, Frances Kemble, undated; 48230 (Box 170, Folder 1a)
  - Stone, David M., undated; 48229 (Box 170, Folder 1b)
  - Stone, Marcus, undated; 48228 (Box 170, Folder 1c)
  - Story, Emelyn, undated; 48227 (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Story, William Wetmore, undated; 48226 (Box 170, Folder 2a)
  - Stout, Rex, undated; 48225 (Box 170, Folder 2b)
  - Stowe, Harriet Elizabeth (Beecher), undated; 48224 (Box 170, Folder 2c)
  - Strachey, John St. Loe, undated; 48223 (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Strachey, Lytton, undated; 48222 (Box 170, Folder 2e)
  - Stratford de Radcliffe, Stratford Canning, undated; 48221 (Box 170, Folder 3a)
  - Straus, Ludwig, undated; 48220 (Box 170, Folder 3b)
  - [Streatfeild, Noel: see Box 171], 1690-2000; 48219 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_6e8c4ae74cc8e75f6a1b04b4ca0508b0)
  - Street, Gladys Bertha, undated; 48218 (Box 170, Folder 3c)
  - Stribling, T.S., undated; 48217 (Box 170, Folder 4a)
  - Strickland, Agnes, undated; 48216 (Box 170, Folder 4b)
  - Strickland, R.P., Rev., undated; 48215 (Box 170, Folder 4c)
  - Strindberg, August, undated; 48214 (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Strindberg, Frida, undated; 48213 (Box 170, Folder 4e)
  - Stringer, Arthur, undated; 48212 (Box 170, Folder 5a)
  - Strutt, Joseph, undated; 48211 (Box 170, Folder 5b)
  - Sturgis, Henry, undated; 48210 (Box 170, Folder 5c)
  - Sue, Euge´ne, undated; 48209 (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Sullivan, Arthur, undated; 48208 (Box 170, Folder 5e)
  - Sullivan, Mark, undated; 48207 (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Sullivan, William, undated; 48206 (Box 170, Folder 6a)
  - Sumner, Charles (1811-1874): [Choate, Rufus], undated; 48205 (Box 170, Folder 6b)
  - Sunderland, D. F., undated; 48204 (Box 170, Folder 6c)
  - Swanberg, W. A., undated; 48203 (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Swenson, May, undated; 48202 (Box 170, Folder 6e)
  - Swinburne, Algernon, undated; 48201 (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Swinnerton, Frank Arthur, undated; 48200 (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - Symington, Andrew James, undated; 48199 (Box 170, Folder 9a)
  - Symonds, John Addington, undated; 48198 (Box 170, Folder 9b)
  - Symons, Alfred James Albert, undated; 48197 (Box 170, Folder 9c)
  - Symons, Arthur, undated; 48196 (Box 170, Folder 10)
  - Streatfeild, Noel: MS. The Magic Summer Chapters 1 - 10, undated; 48195 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - Streatfeild, Noel: MS. The Magic Summer Chapters 11 - 20, undated; 48194 (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - Streatfeild, Noel: MS. The Magic Summer Chapters 21 - 29, undated; 48193 (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - Tabb, John Banister (1844-1909), undated; 48192 (Box 177, Folder 1a)
  - [Taine, John: see Bell, Eric Temple, Box 13.5], 1690-2000; 48191 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_263a1c6cb539d63184677fc3016d928e)
  - Talbot, Catherine (1721-1770), undated; 48190 (Box 177, Folder 1b)
  - Talfourd, Mr.: Correspondence to, undated; 48189 (Box 177, Folder 1c)
  - Talfourd, Francis (1828-1862), undated; 48188 (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - Talfourd, Thomas Noon, Sir (1795-1854): Correspondence from [see also Dickens, Charles: MS. Prologue to Every Man in His Humour], undated; 48187 (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - Talfourd, Thomas Noon, Sir (1795-1854): Correspondence to, undated; 48186 (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - Talfourd, Thomas Noon, Sir (1795-1854): Correspondence to, undated; 48185 (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - Talpur, Faiz Mohammed Khan, Mir (d. 1909), undated; 48184 (Box 177, Folder 5a)
  - Tarbell, Ida M. (1857-1944), undated; 48183 (Box 177, Folder 5b)
  - Tarkington, (Newton) Booth (1869-1946), undated; 48182 (Box 177, Folder 6)
  - Tarkington, (Newton) Booth (1869-1946): MS. Song of the Bead, undated; 48181 (Box 177, Folder 7a)
  - Tarkington, Susannah, undated; 48180 (Box 177, Folder 7b)
  - Tate, Allen, undated; 48179 (Box 177, Folder 8a)
  - Tauscher, Johanna (Gadski) (1871-1932), undated; 48178 (Box 177, Folder 8b)
  - Taylor, Bayard (1825-1878), undated; 48177 (Box 177, Folder 8c)
  - Taylor, Frederick: Scrapbook [including letters], undated; 48176 (Box 177, Folder 9)
  - Taylor, Tom (1817-1880), undated; 48175 (Box 177, Folder 10)
  - Teale, Edwin Way (1899- ), undated; 48174 (Box 177, Folder 11a)
  - Teasdale (Filsinger), Sara (1884-1933), undated; 48173 (Box 177, Folder 11b)
  - Telford, Thomas (1757-1884), undated; 48172 (Box 177, Folder 11c)
  - Tempski, Armine von, undated; 48171 (Box 177, Folder 11)
  - Tenniel, John, Sir (1820-1914), undated; 48170 (Box 177, Folder 12)